http://www.thunderpole.co.uk/privacy.html

Privacy PolicyYour privacy is important to Thunderpole. This privacy policy provides information about the personal information that Thunderpole collects, and the ways in which Thunderpole uses that personal information.Information collected by usIf you have registered with us, or ordered items from us, we may have your email address, telephone number, postal address and the method you chose to make your purchase with. We also collect information about how you use our website, such as the types of content you view or engage with or the frequency and duration of your activities. In addition, our servers, logs, and other technologies automatically collect certain information (see below) to help us administer, protect, and improve our services; analyse usage; and improve users’ experience. We share personal information with others only as described in this policy, or when we believe that the law permits or requires it.Information we collect automaticallyCookies: We may use cookies to collect information about your activity, browser and device. This data helps us to build a profile of our users. Some of this data will be aggregated or statistical, which means that we will not be able to identify you individually. If you prefer, you can remove or reject browser cookies through the settings on your browser or device. However, rejecting or removing cookies could affect the availability and functionality of our services. For further information on our use of cookies, please see our Cookie Policy.Device information: We may also collect information about your device each time you use a site. If you have an account with us, we may collect information from or about the computers, phones or other devices where you log into our services. We may associate the information we collect from your different devices, which helps us provide consistent services across your devices. Here are some examples of the device information that we collect: Attributes such as the operating system and hardware version. Browser type and IP addressLog information: We also collect log information when you use our website. That information includes, among other things: Details about how you’ve engaged with us. Device information, such as web browser type and language. Access times. Pages viewed. IP address. Identifiers associated with cookies or other technologies that may uniquely identify your device or browser. Pages you visit before or after navigating to our website.How we use your personal data1) To make our products and services available to youWe use your personal data to provide you with the information, products and services that you request or purchase from us (i.e. to complete certain tasks, processes or orders on our website, take payment online (where applicable) and deliver your products or services), and to communicate with you regarding those products and services that you purchase from us and respond to your questions and comments;We may also use your personal data to measure how satisfied our customers are and provide customer service (including troubleshooting in connection with purchases or your requests for services or when you ask us questions on social media);2) For administrative and internal business purposesWe may use your personal data for our internal business purposes, such as enhancing our site, improving our services and products and identifying usage trends. We may also use your data to monitor the use of our website and ensure that our website is presented in the most effective and relevant manner for you and your device and setting default options for you (such as language and currency);It is in our legitimate interests as a business to use your personal data in this way. For example, we want to ensure our website is customer friendly and works properly and that our products and services are efficient and of high quality. We also want to make it easy for you to interact with us.3) For security and legal reasonsWe use your personal data to: ensure the personal and financial information you provide us is accurate; conduct fraud checks or prevent other illegal activity; fulfil our legal and compliance-related obligations.In some cases we will use your personal data because it’s necessary for us to comply with a legal obligation (such as if we receive a legitimate request from a law enforcement agency). In other cases (such as the detection of fraud) we will rely on our legitimate interests as a business to use your personal data in this way. 4) To personalise your shopping experience and improve our operationsWe use your personal data to: allow you to create an account on our website which enables you to purchase Thunderpole products and services online without having to fill in your personal data every time you shop online with us; provide you with marketing material via email;It is in our legitimate interests as a business to use your data in this way and we do this in order to enhance your shopping experience with us. This allows us to help you find the products and services which you may be looking for and avoids you having to browse through products or services which are not relevant to you.When we send you marketing material via email, we will rely on our legitimate interests as a business, always ensuring that your rights are protected. You can easily ‘opt out’ of marketing emails by visiting your online account or by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of every email we send out.Who we share your personal information withWe share your data with the following categories of companies as an essential part of being able to provide our services to you: Companies that get your order to you, such as payment service providers and delivery companies. Professional service providers, such as website hosts who help us run our business Law enforcement and fraud prevention agencies, so we can help tackle fraudWe will not share your personal information with any other third party.How long your personal information will be keptWe will hold your information for as long as you have your account, or as long as is needed to be able to provide the services to you, or (in the case of any contact you may have with our Customer Care team) for as long as is necessary to provide support-related reporting and trend analysis only.If reasonably necessary or required to meet legal or regulatory requirements, to comply with HMRC and other tax authorities, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce our terms and conditions, we may also hold some of your information as required, even after you have closed your account or it is no longer needed to provide the services to you.Job applicants, current and former Thunderpole employeesAll the information you provide will only be used for progressing your application, or to fulfil legal or regulatory requirements if necessary.We will not share any of the information you provide during the recruitment process with any third parties for marketing purposes or store any of your information outside of the EEA. The information you provide will be held securely by us and/or our data processors whether the information is in electronic or physical format.We will use the contact details you provide to us to contact you to progress your application. We will use the other information you provide to assess your suitability for the role you have applied for.How long your personal information will be keptWe do not collect more information than we need to fulfil our stated purposes and will not retain it for longer than is necessary. Therefore, if you unsuccessfully apply for a role with us, we will delete or anonymise your personal information once we have communicated this to you. There may be circumstances in which we will retain your data for a future opportunity and if this is the case, we will seek your express consent beforehand.The information we ask for is used to assess your suitability for employment. You do not have to provide what we ask for but it might affect your application if you do not. Within the application stage, we ask for your personal details including name and contact details. We also ask you about your previous experience, education, referees and for answers to questions relevant to the role you have applied for. Our recruitment team will have access to all this information. If we make you a conditional offer of employment we will ask you for information so that we can carry out pre-employment checks. You must successfully complete pre-employment checks to progress to a final offer. We are required to confirm the identity of our employees, their right to work in the United Kingdom and seek assurances as to their trustworthiness, integrity and reliability. Control over your informationUnder the General Data Protection Regulation, you have several important rights available to you for free. In summary, those include rights to: be informed about how your personal information is being used (hopefully this privacy policy explains it all) Access the personal information we hold about you Request us to correct any mistakes in your information which we hold Request the erasure of personal information concerning you in certain situations Receive the personal information concerning you which you have provided to us, in a structured format Stop any direct marketing Object to processing of your personal dataFor further information on each of these rights, including the circumstances in which they apply, see the Guidance from the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) on individuals rights under the General Data Protection Regulation. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please: email, call or write to us at THUNDERPOLE, 1 Hartburn Close, Crow Lane Ind Est, Northampton, NN3 9UE or email info@thunderpole.co.uk, phone +44 (0) 1604 402403 let us have enough information to identify you; let us have proof of your identity and address (a copy of your driving licence or passport and a recent utility or credit card bill); and let us know the information to which your request relatesWe try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made many requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.Keeping your personal information secureWe take data security very seriously. Our website retail system is based on the SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption standard. Provided you are using an SSL-compliant browser, you’ll be able to conduct end-to-end encrypted transactions without fear of an intermediary obtaining your credit card information.We also have appropriate security measures in place to prevent personal information from being accidentally lost, or used or accessed in an unauthorised way. We limit access to your personal information to those who have a genuine business need. Those processing your information will do so only in an authorised manner and are subject to a duty of confidentiality.We also have procedures in place to deal with any suspected data security breach. We will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected data security breach where we are legally required to do so.If you want detailed information from Get Safe Online on how to protect your information and your computers and devices against fraud, identity theft, viruses and many other online problems, please visit www.getsafeonline.org. Get Safe Online is supported by HM Government and leading businesses.How to complainWe hope that we can resolve any query or concern you raise about our use of your information. If you are not happy with how Thunderpole manages your personal data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. The supervisory authority in the UK is the Information Commissioner who may be contacted at https://ico.org.uk/concerns/.Changes to this privacy noticeThis privacy notice was published on 10/05/2018 and last updated on 22/05/2018. Any changes we make to this notice will be posted on this page. Back to Terms and ConditionsSign up for THUNDERPOLE news
Customer ServicesAboutAccountContactDelivery InfoReturnsCookie PolicyPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsVAT Reg No: GB 485 9695 67InformationHelpCB Radio GuideForumSocialLinksTestimonialsUser MapSite MapCategories2-Way RadioAmateur RadioCB RadioMarine RadioScannersTaxi Radio© 1999 - 2020 Astra Communications. All rights reserved. New Account|Sign In|Contact|Help|Forum|Testimonials|£€$ Basket: 0 Items|Total: £0.00CB RadioCB RadiosMobile CB RadiosHandheld CB RadiosCB Radio PacksUsed CB RadiosCB AntennasMobile AntennasHomebase AntennasHandheld AntennasAntenna MountsCB Antenna MountsMounting AccessoriesCB AccessoriesCB MicrophonesExtension SpeakersSWR Meters/MatchersCB DIN MountsCableLeadsCB Power LeadsMic Plugs / ConnectorsRF Plugs / ConnectorsRF Adaptors Switches / Filters   FittingsBracketsHomebase FittingsPower SuppliesVoltage ReducersTest Equipment CB Handheld EssentialsCB Radio Components CB Clothing CB Radio Books CB Antenna Care 2 Way Radio 2-Way RadiosWalkie Talkies Business (Licence-Free)Business (Licensed)Mobile (Licensed)Repeaters (Licensed)2-Way Radio AntennasPMR Handheld AntennasPMR Mobile AntennasPMR Base Station AntennasEar Piece / MicsEarpiecesD Earpieces & MicsG Earpieces & MicsAcoustic Ear & MicsEarpiece & Boom MicsEar Bud & MicsSpeaker MicrophonesHeadsetsFist Mics Peltor HeadsetsAccessoriesChargersBattery PacksRechargeable BattsLeather CasesBelt ClipsAdaptorsAntennasMotorola AccessoriesRadio Flight CasesRadio Din Mounts Panorama Antenna Accessories Amateur RadioAmateur RadiosDual Band Radios70cm Amateur Radios2m Amateur Radios10m Amateur RadiosAmateur AntennasMobile AntennasBase AntennasHandheld AntennasAccessoriesAntenna MountsExtension SpeakersSWR Meters/MatchersAmateur DIN MountsCableLeadsMic Plugs / ConnectorsRF Plugs / ConnectorsRF AdaptorsMicrophonesSwitches / Filters  Homebase FittingsPower SuppliesAmplifiersBattery PacksChargersTest EquipmentClothingAmateur Radio Antenna Care Taxi RadioTaxi RadiosTaxi Mobile AntennasTaxi Base Antennas Taxi Antenna MountsTaxi Antenna AdaptorsTaxi MicrophonesTaxi Power LeadsTaxi Radio FittingsMarine RadioMarine RadiosWaterproof Case with FoamVoltage ReducersWaterproof Radio BagsScanners ScannersRadio ScannersAntennas / FittingsHandheld AntennasMobile AntennasHomebase AntennasHomebase FittingsAccessoriesEar PiecesClip-on SpeakersLeads / CablePlugs / AdaptorsBattery PacksRechargeable BattsMisc Wi-Fi AntennasWi-Fi Antennas
